{"traceId":"a56477ad40903e8ede0ab277f501bcd7","name":"crypto randomUUID","id":"d11c7894a2944aa1","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639825000,"duration":357.292,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"crypto","preflight.crypto.function":"randomUUID","preflight.crypto.args":"[]","preflight.crypto.response":"\"7652a15e-4513-4cbc-8e75-233692845f4f\""},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"1fa0dc69ea1f4c01","name":"pg.connect","id":"c7c21e557ac45c00","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639831000,"duration":27172.333,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"1fa0dc69ea1f4c01","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639830000,"duration":30121.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"065883a6404d8af7306f1ceccdc59f7b","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"e8a0a8ab3de4f15f","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639863000,"duration":6994.542,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_SCHEMA\" ( \"className\" varChar(120), \"schema\" jsonb, \"isParseClass\" bool, PRIMARY KEY (\"className\") )","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"c7c21e557ac45c00","name":"Date.now","id":"7928150926ac8d24","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639872000,"duration":498.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639872"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"d557a9e9b4375aa7d4e10f6b152ab2eb","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"136daa9932d91e0e","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639876000,"duration":17128.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"3bd93bb0c834709cc19f0a6429d72640","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"5e254ef1bdc98eea","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639905000,"duration":2748.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_Hooks\" (\"functionName\" text,\"className\" text,\"triggerName\" text,\"url\" text)","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"c7c21e557ac45c00","name":"Date.now","id":"a92b5e8284676809","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639911000,"duration":394.291,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639911"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"461777beb1b788a33f21a1915dc963a6","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"3f631824a6368e3a","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639914000,"duration":4318.958,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"c7c21e557ac45c00","name":"Date.now","id":"345962ad6ac3f606","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639922000,"duration":368.292,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639922"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"879898e222f7f01d33f8212de1fa4be1","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"5d01a807ab9a5d38","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639926000,"duration":3695.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"c7c21e557ac45c00","name":"Date.now","id":"ba617ed027162cf9","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639932000,"duration":46.25,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639932"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"512e8455fa7fee74d60a2afa07a67857","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"eae836ef9113d0b9","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639934000,"duration":107.625,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","parentId":"d0c14494663f7094","name":"pg.connect","id":"c8f149050ba9b894","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639898000,"duration":38678.208,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"d0c14494663f7094","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639880000,"duration":57274.625,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","parentId":"a3e2125b16c21067","name":"pg.connect","id":"b9d9b0676c29eb63","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639902000,"duration":37584.875,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"a3e2125b16c21067","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639888000,"duration":51874.458,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","parentId":"ca5b797545b092ff","name":"pg.connect","id":"ee2a07286478582d","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639900000,"duration":40372.709,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"ca5b797545b092ff","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639885000,"duration":56421.833,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","parentId":"b43288eb20775102","name":"pg.connect","id":"003a14ba30729af4","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639896000,"duration":46478.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"b43288eb20775102","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639877000,"duration":65323.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","parentId":"9240647253acbc8c","name":"pg.connect","id":"e6ceb04b9c89fae3","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639899000,"duration":45005.834,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"9240647253acbc8c","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639883000,"duration":61712.542,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"1b525289b096fed5","name":"pg.connect","id":"c349e5e68979b6f4","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639896000,"duration":49209.125,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"1b525289b096fed5","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639879000,"duration":67479.167,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"3ac577db034e8a43d4e80bda0c06720f","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"cf5f5c09186af6b7","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639939000,"duration":8885.583,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_PushStatus\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"createdAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"updatedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"pushTime\" text,\"source\" text,\"query\" text,\"payload\" text,\"title\" text,\"expiry\" double precision,\"expiration_interval\" double precision,\"status\" text,\"numSent\" double precision,\"numFailed\" double precision,\"pushHash\" text,\"errorMessage\" jsonb,\"sentPerType\" jsonb,\"failedPerType\" jsonb,\"sentPerUTCOffset\" jsonb,\"failedPerUTCOffset\" jsonb,\"count\" double precision,\"_rperm\" text[],\"_wperm\" text[])","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","parentId":"c8f149050ba9b894","name":"Date.now","id":"937274bc9954aff4","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639949000,"duration":29.292,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639949"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"821c02657c4162fc995852ce59699b78","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"30dc708c80135979","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639940000,"duration":9234.084,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_Audience\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"createdAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"updatedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"name\" text,\"query\" text,\"lastUsed\" timestamp with time zone,\"timesUsed\" double precision,\"_rperm\" text[],\"_wperm\" text[])","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","parentId":"b9d9b0676c29eb63","name":"Date.now","id":"740ed26a1d22a902","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639950000,"duration":16.334,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639950"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7f8305afaf5601390f7535bfc043a0c0","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"e428e0484c75c3e2","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639942000,"duration":9008.125,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_GraphQLConfig\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"config\" jsonb)","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","parentId":"ee2a07286478582d","name":"Date.now","id":"4a39ca491d8e3818","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639952000,"duration":26.125,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639952"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"07aa254faeaf9946c02d52d2a30cad9b","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"aa616eca0a57c2c0","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639943000,"duration":9802.208,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_JobStatus\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"createdAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"updatedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"jobName\" text,\"source\" text,\"status\" text,\"message\" text,\"params\" jsonb,\"finishedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"_rperm\" text[],\"_wperm\" text[])","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","parentId":"003a14ba30729af4","name":"Date.now","id":"d9ac44791441912d","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639953000,"duration":12.75,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639953"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"d32648c455504cbce09986cd04708b63","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"69138c14d80fc024","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639945000,"duration":8817.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_GlobalConfig\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"params\" jsonb,\"masterKeyOnly\" jsonb)","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","parentId":"e6ceb04b9c89fae3","name":"Date.now","id":"befc085120d0081c","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639954000,"duration":28.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639954"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","parentId":"3ad258b8f692be7c","name":"pg.connect","id":"b05d72cb96acd895","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639902000,"duration":54621.125,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","preflight.library":"pg"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"3ad258b8f692be7c","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639891000,"duration":66177.792,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"50a958f54b7ea1aea9748965e8435c14","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"e6ec7bd9cc90a766","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639949000,"duration":10361.834,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","parentId":"c8f149050ba9b894","name":"Date.now","id":"55373792883164d6","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639960000,"duration":66.5,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639960"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"97e4bd1b1e406ba1354eaf795bbc1ee1","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"4351ea545916420e","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639950000,"duration":11121.833,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","parentId":"b9d9b0676c29eb63","name":"Date.now","id":"7c6e02ff2ab378f4","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639961000,"duration":12.75,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639962"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5705826a905594f6be3b86f25b4d5cea","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"de755513bc3cfeff","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639952000,"duration":10864.791,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","parentId":"ee2a07286478582d","name":"Date.now","id":"2822d31daae7c721","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639964000,"duration":69.417,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639964"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"dd68d28728c5cf34faa2101e6c90537d","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"f173cc796fcc5d15","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639953000,"duration":10972.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","parentId":"003a14ba30729af4","name":"Date.now","id":"5db4e7721ec69610","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639964000,"duration":10.292,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639964"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"46de7a74c4e3ded40c8f031d71883573","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"94f7c95be804c6b8","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639955000,"duration":9080.916,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","parentId":"e6ceb04b9c89fae3","name":"Date.now","id":"b89568c54ddfd521","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639965000,"duration":10.792,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639965"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e05378e4f817fdfe2a0d1864b634dac8","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"75599810e73105c7","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639958000,"duration":6683.875,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_Idempotency\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"createdAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"updatedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"reqId\" text,\"expire\" timestamp with time zone,\"_rperm\" text[],\"_wperm\" text[])","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","parentId":"b05d72cb96acd895","name":"Date.now","id":"549b4b45f1ea3226","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639965000,"duration":9.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639965"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"55532d569da179853d7f17ebf0097ea1","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"f45982210a2d3df4","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639947000,"duration":18863.166,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE TABLE IF NOT EXISTS \"_JobSchedule\" (\"objectId\" text,PRIMARY KEY (\"objectId\"),\"createdAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"updatedAt\" timestamp with time zone,\"jobName\" text,\"description\" text,\"params\" text,\"startAfter\" text,\"daysOfWeek\" jsonb,\"timeOfDay\" text,\"lastRun\" double precision,\"repeatMinutes\" double precision,\"_rperm\" text[],\"_wperm\" text[])","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"08be2a8a7120bd38","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639966000,"duration":19.292,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639966"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"8eececcef15897a42f076ca12cb7b3e5","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"440feb32adda00c3","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639961000,"duration":5743.833,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","parentId":"c8f149050ba9b894","name":"Date.now","id":"525f335ca297b1ac","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639967000,"duration":12.208,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639967"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c640386caf0eb70c431b60547a63fb2c","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"1f7daddfef1b26a5","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639968000,"duration":449.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"6b9117817b243d85b4dfd948121c25bb","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"7937585fd2211703","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639962000,"duration":8948.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","parentId":"b9d9b0676c29eb63","name":"Date.now","id":"0b8f5b4d118f09e2","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639971000,"duration":100.75,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639971"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"31201671621490f70aade2b3ea08db05","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"2109867628e7a030","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639973000,"duration":246.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"533a37c8c869cfccaf8b48694b701859","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"ca37e0917d23083b","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639964000,"duration":11506.125,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","parentId":"ee2a07286478582d","name":"Date.now","id":"81c2df95080f5d1a","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639976000,"duration":87.084,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639976"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e13a09e80d405005a294489d6041139f","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"fba204e4eefbba3a","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639977000,"duration":226,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"1a2e278311da795bbfbbc56865fe2797","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"7dd4527da673618a","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639964000,"duration":16037.583,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","parentId":"003a14ba30729af4","name":"Date.now","id":"743d5ebcac855cc6","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639981000,"duration":134.167,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639981"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"f692b5a1e4d04a93ce3d25b80ff2944a","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"7d92df4a5bb7ab15","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639983000,"duration":262.709,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"f836656a48996ab9404563e1b614657d","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"a140baa8ec32bc01","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639965000,"duration":21570.625,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","parentId":"e6ceb04b9c89fae3","name":"Date.now","id":"aa40169a37797a18","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639987000,"duration":113.833,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639987"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"bef78921e3f82693e7579774885ccb19","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"19ee3b0914a784c9","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639988000,"duration":183.834,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e3eb3811ae2c21d8a86941cbe5b939c7","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"4aaa4fdfa1acb235","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639966000,"duration":23159.75,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","parentId":"b05d72cb96acd895","name":"Date.now","id":"aa346614260f1dde","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639990000,"duration":13.084,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639990"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e735b6d6e71a1ea5daf13bb526cdde36","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"7ae248065288171b","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639966000,"duration":23847.75,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"3bf6d7e72730e73e","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639990000,"duration":9.75,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639990"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"afa2433bfed92f374721522c8c8b846a","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"f8ac1452cadffa6b","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639935000,"duration":55292.458,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_Hooks'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":4,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"functionName\"},{\"column_name\":\"className\"},{\"column_name\":\"triggerName\"},{\"column_name\":\"url\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"94a6bec2cc7d796550361a11bd46fa42","parentId":"c7c21e557ac45c00","name":"Date.now","id":"ba26fb707bee7418","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639991000,"duration":11.125,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639991"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"970eaa704512fb4646443d28eb1b4bd0","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"de6ecfce712159aa","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639970000,"duration":21843.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_PushStatus'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":22,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"numFailed\"},{\"column_name\":\"createdAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"errorMessage\"},{\"column_name\":\"sentPerType\"},{\"column_name\":\"failedPerType\"},{\"column_name\":\"sentPerUTCOffset\"},{\"column_name\":\"failedPerUTCOffset\"},{\"column_name\":\"count\"},{\"column_name\":\"expiry\"},{\"column_name\":\"expiration_interval\"},{\"column_name\":\"updatedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"numSent\"},{\"column_name\":\"_wperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"pushTime\"},{\"column_name\":\"source\"},{\"column_name\":\"query\"},{\"column_name\":\"payload\"},{\"column_name\":\"title\"},{\"column_name\":\"status\"},{\"column_name\":\"pushHash\"},{\"column_name\":\"_rperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4cadc7f4a930bf072cd62d9287d13404","parentId":"c8f149050ba9b894","name":"Date.now","id":"30d5a9e214de4abf","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639993000,"duration":184.459,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639993"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"3f614f3a944afa584fdec9c9048b9dbe","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"2535358b877ec890","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639975000,"duration":19844.542,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_Audience'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":9,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"lastUsed\"},{\"column_name\":\"timesUsed\"},{\"column_name\":\"createdAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"updatedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"},{\"column_name\":\"_wperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"name\"},{\"column_name\":\"query\"},{\"column_name\":\"_rperm\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"5fcf19d542239b2094cd34d0f26ffa49","parentId":"b9d9b0676c29eb63","name":"Date.now","id":"d4a75be101ffd783","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639995000,"duration":12.834,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639995"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"f98fbe34b1a5c3449180b7b3bbec8937","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"09ef3f96ea439107","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639979000,"duration":17257.833,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_GraphQLConfig'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":2,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"config\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4be4ed88378fb07308f82ce986eac973","parentId":"ee2a07286478582d","name":"Date.now","id":"3561e3c0c314b1ef","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639997000,"duration":94.166,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639997"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c92049f8ff0cf419766366809142a630","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"0f9a3b9c3aad9475","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639985000,"duration":12248.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_JobStatus'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":11,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"params\"},{\"column_name\":\"finishedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"createdAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"updatedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"message\"},{\"column_name\":\"_rperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"},{\"column_name\":\"_wperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"jobName\"},{\"column_name\":\"source\"},{\"column_name\":\"status\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"0ea927352914dc0f9e84c172c16c2eed","parentId":"003a14ba30729af4","name":"Date.now","id":"acc9acb52d386285","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639997000,"duration":11.083,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639997"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"ec215bfa6c0d1701c3159486634d2398","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"11dfaefd00a46932","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639989000,"duration":8862.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_GlobalConfig'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":3,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"params\"},{\"column_name\":\"masterKeyOnly\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a71ca6cdee42c03580d0bf93f059f13d","parentId":"e6ceb04b9c89fae3","name":"Date.now","id":"6a4b3fd777a29c61","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639998000,"duration":11.167,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639998"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c85861ccabcdfd964be07250838e0cc7","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"86da9415a8aebe10","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639990000,"duration":8642.542,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","parentId":"b05d72cb96acd895","name":"Date.now","id":"4b2d3aad4c5ccce1","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786639999000,"duration":92.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786639999"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"bff158a760d7ec69271e31f0741a9a67","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"07b73601eba8cb40","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640001000,"duration":191.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7fd2de59e8e7b872cfe822b1cd9c2fd5","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"fd44a3c3ae3e7ee8","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786639990000,"duration":13796.958,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"544903f78723f0d1","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640005000,"duration":139.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640005"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4c231de18d6eaba85d74c738142a6388","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"a9aaaef515715677","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640007000,"duration":447.334,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c0f32329c51bcdc3144d3623bbcf68d5","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"b02c9dc6e44e6840","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640003000,"duration":9436.75,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_Idempotency'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":7,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"expire\"},{\"column_name\":\"updatedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"createdAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"_wperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"reqId\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"},{\"column_name\":\"_rperm\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a4a33cd1b735afca170568094a597bd4","parentId":"b05d72cb96acd895","name":"Date.now","id":"a61c3c301fba682d","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640013000,"duration":89.209,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640013"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"dec8c5274c23017711100453af16c5e4","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"4cc4bc0b01f2c6b2","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640010000,"duration":6545.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT column_name FROM information_schema.columns WHERE table_name = '_JobSchedule'","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":13,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"column_name\":\"createdAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"lastRun\"},{\"column_name\":\"repeatMinutes\"},{\"column_name\":\"updatedAt\"},{\"column_name\":\"daysOfWeek\"},{\"column_name\":\"timeOfDay\"},{\"column_name\":\"_rperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"objectId\"},{\"column_name\":\"_wperm\"},{\"column_name\":\"jobName\"},{\"column_name\":\"description\"},{\"column_name\":\"params\"},{\"column_name\":\"startAfter\"}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"955a8059ce62a889","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640018000,"duration":92.959,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640018"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"9b249727bf15fa60bf25e7366e0d2cdc","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"1c97c28f1454678d","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640019000,"duration":250.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"ddcc8349c0c2390fe6585ff6c39943ca","name":"pg.query:BEGIN postgres","id":"e39e36659aefac2e","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640020000,"duration":833.208,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"begin","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"BEGIN","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"560a80e77fa81dd4","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640021000,"duration":12.542,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640021"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"dc7d98651752ab228b240680cb1c2cae","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"b4e5ef3a5a354122","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640021000,"duration":3773.166,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION json_object_set_key( \"json\" jsonb, key_to_set TEXT, value_to_set anyelement ) RETURNS jsonb LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT concat('{', string_agg(to_json(\"key\") || ':' || \"value\", ','), '}')::jsonb FROM (SELECT * FROM jsonb_each(\"json\") WHERE key <> key_to_set UNION ALL SELECT key_to_set, to_json(\"value_to_set\")::jsonb) AS fields $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"2ad750d5c1d41640","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640025000,"duration":12.041,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640025"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"8227173fdaeb1bb2053458bb81d8f8bc","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"9c68b8ee818253b8","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640026000,"duration":2839.958,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_add( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS jsonb LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT array_to_json(ARRAY(SELECT unnest(ARRAY(SELECT DISTINCT jsonb_array_elements(\"array\")) || ARRAY(SELECT jsonb_array_elements(\"values\")))))::jsonb; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"062b05054a16fd9b","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640030000,"duration":88.208,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640030"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"319b2843c38bc67834f71f8d1cade9d7","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"de550124ce7120b4","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640031000,"duration":390.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_add_unique( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS jsonb LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT array_to_json(ARRAY(SELECT DISTINCT unnest(ARRAY(SELECT DISTINCT jsonb_array_elements(\"array\")) || ARRAY(SELECT DISTINCT jsonb_array_elements(\"values\")))))::jsonb; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"044f0058c376d3b7","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640031000,"duration":11.583,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640031"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"56b5d4b60d2361b64a7024237739ce60","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"8d61ae9480f6059d","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640031000,"duration":394.208,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_remove( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS jsonb LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT array_to_json(ARRAY(SELECT * FROM jsonb_array_elements(\"array\") as elt WHERE elt NOT IN (SELECT * FROM (SELECT jsonb_array_elements(\"values\")) AS sub)))::jsonb; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"b10b6718e9df8e5f","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640032000,"duration":10.25,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640032"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"17c89a5fcc76018807b087b8edd1364c","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"27d6e6fe1fdadfa3","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640032000,"duration":821.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_contains_all( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS boolean LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT CASE WHEN 0 = jsonb_array_length(\"values\") THEN true = false ELSE (SELECT RES.CNT = jsonb_array_length(\"values\") FROM (SELECT COUNT(*) as CNT FROM jsonb_array_elements_text(\"array\") as elt WHERE elt IN (SELECT jsonb_array_elements_text(\"values\"))) as RES) END; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"0b7039c2c882245c","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640033000,"duration":9.542,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640033"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"3a8bf55af91f05a744bb40f6bedc8006","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"dd21c83d4af3d2be","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640033000,"duration":260.792,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_contains_all_regex( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS boolean LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT CASE WHEN 0 = jsonb_array_length(\"values\") THEN true = false ELSE (SELECT RES.CNT = jsonb_array_length(\"values\") FROM (SELECT COUNT(*) as CNT FROM jsonb_array_elements_text(\"array\") as elt WHERE elt LIKE ANY (SELECT jsonb_array_elements_text(\"values\"))) as RES) END; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"4c23736c9b95b0d2","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640033000,"duration":9.25,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640033"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"f2ccf0db38b7fbf30fdaf98be53139a4","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"acff3af6339cb009","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640033000,"duration":221.084,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION array_contains( \"array\" jsonb, \"values\" jsonb ) RETURNS boolean LANGUAGE sql IMMUTABLE STRICT AS $function$ SELECT RES.CNT >= 1 FROM (SELECT COUNT(*) as CNT FROM jsonb_array_elements(\"array\") as elt WHERE elt IN (SELECT jsonb_array_elements(\"values\"))) as RES; $function$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"5027bd75b262920e","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640034000,"duration":9,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640034"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"03ef614135b363dd436110eab6a92d80","name":"pg.query:COMMIT postgres","id":"7bc75533d8917222","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640034000,"duration":496.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"commit","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"COMMIT","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"d161a64929fe8e9c","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640034000,"duration":11.5,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640034"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"af21c109286bc2becface491f2fe722a","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"f3a9f616d8175804","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640036000,"duration":272,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"4f5d4ebccc7f45f8897dc0143b1146fc","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"6e5d8ea67f1453c7","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640038000,"duration":2302.959,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT * FROM \"_SCHEMA\"","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":3,"preflight.pg.rows":"[{\"className\":\"_User\",\"schema\":{\"fields\":{\"email\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"_rperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"_wperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"authData\":{\"type\":\"Object\"},\"objectId\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"username\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"createdAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"},\"updatedAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"},\"emailVerified\":{\"type\":\"Boolean\"},\"_hashed_password\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"className\":\"_User\"},\"isParseClass\":true},{\"className\":\"_Role\",\"schema\":{\"fields\":{\"name\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"roles\":{\"type\":\"Relation\",\"targetClass\":\"_Role\"},\"users\":{\"type\":\"Relation\",\"targetClass\":\"_User\"},\"_rperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"_wperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"objectId\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"createdAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"},\"updatedAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"}},\"className\":\"_Role\"},\"isParseClass\":true},{\"className\":\"GameScore\",\"schema\":{\"fields\":{\"score\":{\"type\":\"Number\"},\"_rperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"_wperm\":{\"type\":\"Array\",\"contents\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"objectId\":{\"type\":\"String\"},\"cheatMode\":{\"type\":\"Boolean\"},\"createdAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"},\"updatedAt\":{\"type\":\"Date\"},\"playerName\":{\"type\":\"String\"}},\"className\":\"GameScore\"},\"isParseClass\":true}]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"9346a8424bf955c7","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640045000,"duration":170.125,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640045"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"2dc06d623f0b7d36e7bec9ea74e61b58","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"1507519b89c027ae","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640049000,"duration":503.834,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"038c1b8bf23dc4dc354ed189869c2a83","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"59b88b959fa09965","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640051000,"duration":2633.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE UNIQUE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"_User_unique_username\" ON \"_User\"(\"username\")","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"0c62bd7feb2c26c3","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640055000,"duration":94.959,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640055"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"9b242598f8c486feac1f499fc94ba53b","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"4bfe4f591c97db78","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640056000,"duration":257.042,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"3c73b41f4f8cb4c2f7996708a7d6683f","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"2154fe8812b9fdf5","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640057000,"duration":1251.083,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"case_insensitive_username\" ON \"_User\" (lower(\"username\") varchar_pattern_ops)","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"977d1d8e831ca367","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640059000,"duration":13.416,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640059"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"24c9d310ec8d4c16e3842657f1367bfc","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"749deac1c378dc3f","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640059000,"duration":150.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"75902bf4e1fd2d4cda3d6e9cd7155bd9","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"bd82235e3242aefd","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640063000,"duration":604.5,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"case_insensitive_email\" ON \"_User\" (lower(\"email\") varchar_pattern_ops)","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"22bdc65f44d77962","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640063000,"duration":10.541,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640063"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"9cbd97843dbe01ecdd2efaf84d40bb5b","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"09d9cedf57707a34","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640063000,"duration":59.916,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"69d707f61942ffcd690ef83342c47065","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"04d8b329963cdfbf","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640064000,"duration":412.75,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE UNIQUE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"_User_unique_email\" ON \"_User\"(\"email\")","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"769e4cba36e10a05","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640064000,"duration":9,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640064"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"75c92e949c838e66afc4e68d6003a0a6","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"e5d8194bda7e1012","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640064000,"duration":44.5,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"a5b31999d38b055c9a62b1d8a4f45dda","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"b13fc2fdd806ba12","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640064000,"duration":375.75,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE UNIQUE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"_Role_unique_name\" ON \"_Role\"(\"name\")","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"96d53b5070567284","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640065000,"duration":8.333,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640065"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e56da8750f050a0c508e5775a57bd3f5","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"339d93aaec49a75f","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640065000,"duration":43.417,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"b79a534053521ba529c8fd9a3959e687","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"218fb1a8364a7365","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640065000,"duration":350.792,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE UNIQUE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"_Idempotency_unique_reqId\" ON \"_Idempotency\"(\"reqId\")","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"c636c3ad8a2d04ea","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640065000,"duration":10.958,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640065"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"f49d23411f96a08fbcfa02af327e4d22","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"f8cbd569acbb8bbc","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640066000,"duration":53.917,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c69a64808f3f0d305a1a05f465727960","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"6af73bc8ec325d69","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640066000,"duration":4553.916,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE OR REPLACE FUNCTION idempotency_delete_expired_records() RETURNS void LANGUAGE plpgsql AS $$ BEGIN DELETE FROM \"_Idempotency\" WHERE expire < NOW() - INTERVAL '300 seconds'; END; $$;","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"403ff0fed54027e0","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640071000,"duration":8.667,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640071"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"e2726031bab1ef03f94b1d434af4de12","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"23e5536dd936a25f","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640071000,"duration":321.541,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"8cc45b3c0e658ba921ca2b46f652f1b3","name":"pg.query:CREATE postgres","id":"448f95ee563008b0","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640071000,"duration":459.25,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"CREATE INDEX IF NOT EXISTS \"ttl\" ON \"_Idempotency\" (\"expire\")","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"CREATE","preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"d315d209e393258d","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640072000,"duration":11.917,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640072"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"fd8b486a20c79b611054539a34e35608","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"a500c32b6de81456","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640074000,"duration":209.583,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"06c58e846790f69e651d980843851c82","name":"pg.query:SELECT postgres","id":"6aae649c2e3b4ee0","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786640074000,"duration":546.375,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"SELECT * FROM \"_Hooks\"    ","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"SELECT","preflight.pg.rowCount":0,"preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"7d7cffad7c39b563662d74cefccce1cd","parentId":"c349e5e68979b6f4","name":"Date.now","id":"35d1a226bee91791","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786640075000,"duration":11.5,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786640075"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"new Date","id":"3775f2a2fa863db9","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646459000,"duration":44.708,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"Date.new","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"\"2024-06-07T18:57:26.459Z\""},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"Date.now","id":"c360bc1df7eb939c","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646459000,"duration":15.25,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786646459"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"new Date","id":"475a22e7a664782d","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646461000,"duration":18.375,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"Date.new","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"\"2024-06-07T18:57:26.461Z\""},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"crypto randomBytes","id":"cde43c591b6c10e1","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646463000,"duration":61.167,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"crypto","preflight.crypto.function":"randomBytes","preflight.crypto.args":"[10]","preflight.crypto.response":"{\"type\":\"Buffer\",\"data\":[190,187,235,87,127,236,29,242,197,39]}"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"pg-pool.connect","id":"d6868c00705cc97b","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786646465000,"duration":658.292,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.postgresql.idle.timeout.millis":10000},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"new Date","id":"299cf51e997e3d81","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646465000,"duration":14.625,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"Date.new","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"\"2024-06-07T18:57:26.465Z\""},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"Date.now","id":"1d41eb5b4a644f9c","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646466000,"duration":11.917,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786646466"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"pg.query:INSERT postgres","id":"9e1cf792c7416a26","kind":2,"timestamp":1717786646466000,"duration":3671.625,"attributes":{"db.system":"postgresql","db.name":"postgres","db.connection_string":"postgresql://localhost:5431/postgres","net.peer.name":"localhost","net.peer.port":5431,"db.user":"postgres","db.statement":"INSERT INTO \"GameScore\" (\"score\",\"playerName\",\"cheatMode\",\"updatedAt\",\"createdAt\",\"objectId\") VALUES (1337,'Sean Plott',false,'2024-06-07T18:57:26.461Z','2024-06-07T18:57:26.461Z','EBxZDyd4Ln')","preflight.library":"pg","preflight.pg.command":"INSERT","preflight.pg.rowCount":1,"preflight.pg.rows":"[]"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"Date.now","id":"7cd5564ba6507a3b","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646470000,"duration":17.208,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786646470"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"new Date","id":"f0bdf45447a73c22","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646471000,"duration":19.167,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"Date.new","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"\"2024-06-07T18:57:26.471Z\""},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","parentId":"8460b41e4bd004e2","name":"Date.now","id":"ecbb62b722eec713","kind":0,"timestamp":1717786646473000,"duration":17.125,"attributes":{"preflight.library":"date","preflight.date.function":"now","preflight.date.args":"[]","preflight.date.response":"1717786646473"},"status":{"code":1},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
{"traceId":"c04b241fc667089b774d38e2117f4940","name":"POST","id":"8460b41e4bd004e2","kind":1,"timestamp":1717786646431000,"duration":46464.833,"attributes":{"http.url":"http://localhost:1337/parse/classes/GameScore","http.host":"localhost:1337","net.host.name":"localhost","http.method":"POST","http.scheme":"http","http.target":"/parse/classes/GameScore","http.user_agent":"curl/8.4.0","http.request_content_length_uncompressed":58,"http.flavor":"1.1","net.transport":"ip_tcp","http.request.body":"{\"score\":1337,\"playerName\":\"Sean Plott\",\"cheatMode\":false}","http.response.body":"{\"objectId\":\"EBxZDyd4Ln\",\"createdAt\":\"2024-06-07T18:57:26.461Z\"}","net.host.ip":"127.0.0.1","net.host.port":1337,"net.peer.ip":"127.0.0.1","net.peer.port":61757,"http.status_code":201,"http.status_text":"CREATED","http.request.path":"/parse/classes/:className","http.request.headers":"{\"host\":\"localhost:1337\",\"user-agent\":\"curl/8.4.0\",\"accept\":\"*/*\",\"x-parse-application-id\":\"APP_ID\",\"x-parse-master-key\":\"MASTER_KEY\",\"content-type\":\"application/json\",\"content-length\":\"58\"}","http.response.headers":"{\"x-powered-by\":\"Express\",\"access-control-allow-origin\":\"*\",\"access-control-allow-methods\":\"GET,PUT,POST,DELETE,OPTIONS\",\"access-control-allow-headers\":\"X-Parse-Master-Key, X-Parse-REST-API-Key, X-Parse-Javascript-Key, X-Parse-Application-Id, X-Parse-Client-Version, X-Parse-Session-Token, X-Requested-With, X-Parse-Revocable-Session, X-Parse-Request-Id, Content-Type, Pragma, Cache-Control\",\"access-control-expose-headers\":\"X-Parse-Job-Status-Id, X-Parse-Push-Status-Id\",\"location\":\"http://localhost:1337/parse/classes/GameScore/EBxZDyd4Ln\",\"content-type\":\"application/json; charset=utf-8\",\"content-length\":\"64\",\"etag\":\"W/\\\"40-fvThwXESakFYzAjR1rr7FvYEK8w\\\"\"}","preflight.library":"http","preflight.environment":"{}"},"status":{"code":0},"events":[],"resource":{"_attributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"},"asyncAttributesPending":false,"_syncAttributes":{"service.name":"@preflight/service","telemetry.sdk.language":"nodejs","telemetry.sdk.name":"opentelemetry","telemetry.sdk.version":"1.17.0"}}}
